{
  "quiz": [{
      "question": "What does HTML stand for?",
      "options": [
        "Home Tool Markup Language",
        "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language"
      ],
      "answer": "1"
    }, {
      "question": "Dion is looking for a job that better matches his skills and interests.",
      "options": [
        "Cyclical",
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Cyclical",
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Cyclical",
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural"
      ],
      "answer": "1"
    },

    {
      "question": "Christine recently retired from her job as a computer programmer.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Structural",
        "Frictional",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "0"
    }, {
      "question": "Joseph quit his job as a store clerk and is taking a month to travel Europe prior to starting his new job in advertising.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Cyclical",
        "Structural"
      ],
      "answer": "1"
    },

    {
      "question": "Dana lost her job because she could not operate a new drill that the company installed.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Cyclical",
        "Structural"
      ],
      "answer": "2"
    },

    {
      "question": "Eric lost his job when it was outsourced to the Bahamas.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Cyclical",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural"
      ],
      "answer": "2"
    },

    {
      "question": "The recent downturn in the economy causes Adriana to lose her job.",
      "options": [
        "Structural",
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "3"
    },

    {
      "question": "Francesca is a homemaker who quit her job to stay home with her children.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "0"
    },

    {
      "question": "Brittany lost his job when a mild recession hit to the economy.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "3"
    },

    {
      "question": "Ricci lost her job because she could not move to Texas when the company relocated.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "2"
    },

    {
      "question": "Giselle lost her job as a New York magazine ad editor when consumers and businesses switched to internet advertising.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "2"
    },

    {
      "question": "In search of a better opportunity for promotion, Misty left her job in Florida and moved to New York.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "1"
    },

    {
      "question": "Victoria was laid off her construction job because of a colder than normal winter.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "2"
    },

    {
      "question": "Devan believes she will never find a job that matches her skills so she quit looking.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "0"
    },

    {
      "question": "When consumers lost half of their real wealth as a result of a general decline in the stock market, Naomi lost her job.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "3"
    },

    {
      "question": "Nicole was laid off from her job as a swimming pool designer when people quit buying swimming pools because their real incomes decreased.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "3"
    },

    {
      "question": "Soya, a recent college graduate, is searching for her first job.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "1"
    },

    {
      "question": "Katya was unable to operate the new computers that were installed in her office so she was laid off.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "2"
    },

    {
      "question": "Stephanie lost her job as a wild land firefighter when the weather turned cold.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "2"
    },

    {
      "question": "Ricardo refuses to work for minimum wage.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "1"
    },

    {
      "question": "Sales are down all over Crowntown.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "3"
    },

    {
      "question": "Todd was unable to work with customers at the front desk so he lost his job.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "2"
    },

    {
      "question": "Greg is trying to find a job that pays more than he earned in his last position.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "1"
    },

    {
      "question": "A discouraged worker is no longer looking for a job.",
      "options": [
        "Not Unemployed",
        "Frictional",
        "Structural",
        "Cyclical"
      ],
      "answer": "0"
    }
  ]
}
